埃文  我知道你没拿到蓝带
Evan, I know you're disappointed
失望极了
that you didn't get your blue belt.
说实话  我挺好的
Actually, I'm cool.
我会把它看做我人生旅途的一部分
I've accepted it as a part of life's journey.
得了吧  埃文  我们是一队的
Come on, Evan. We're a team.
你不可能是这么想的
That can't be how you really feel.
你说对了  是我妈让我这么说的
You're right. My mom told me to say that.
你想象不到我以前都把什么看做了
You wouldn't believe the things I've accepted
人生旅途的一部分
as part of life's journey.
但我真的很想拿到蓝腰带
But I really do want my blue belt.
那我们就要释放出你的龙之真气
Then we've got to unleash your inner dragon.
你也听见老师这么讲了
You heard the sensei.
如果你下节课之前
If you don't become a blue belt
拿不到蓝带的话  我们就要甩下你调课了
by our next class, we move on without you.
嘿  别因为我水平差劲
Hey, just because I stink
就以为我听不懂人话
doesn't mean I don't understand English.
我们要让你足够愤怒
We are gonna get you angry enough
来释放你积攒已久的龙气
to release all your pent up inner aggression.
这是你妈让你带着的
This is the new balance plate lunchbox
营养均衡板午餐盒  对吗
your mom made you get, right?
但你想不想要酷到让人大跌眼镜的
But didn't you want the cool ufc lunchbox
终极格斗赛特款午餐盒呢
with the dude's eyeball falling out?
我妈认为那种太暴力了
My mom thought it was too violent.
再说了  这款有个胡萝卜暖瓶呢
Plus, this one had a carrot thermos.
埃文  如果你想要格斗锦标赛午餐盒
Evan, if you want that cool ufc lunchbox,
你就得把营养均衡饭盒砸了
you need to smash the balance plate.
来吧  伙计  深吸一口气再呼出点火苗来
Come on, dude. Reach down deep and breathe some fire.
你知道的  我还是别这么做了
You know, I better not.
我妈说如果我不把它带回家
Mom says if I don't bring it home,
我就吃不到甜品了
I don't get my dessert.
而你是知道我多喜欢生杏仁的
And you know how I love raw almonds.